- 이봐, 뉴스가 있어
- 뭔데?
-Guys, guess what?
-What?
오늘 밤 할로윈 파티를 열기로 했어
We're having a Halloween party!
- 좋았어!
- 재밌겠는데!
-Good!
-Great!
- 다들 분장을 해야 돼
- 난 딴 약속 있어
-You have to wear a costume.
-I can't make it.
왜 그래, 재밌을 거야
Come on, it'll be fun.
난 참석할게, 강의하러 갈 때
어차피 분장하고 가야 돼
I'll be there. I have to wear a
costume to my classes that day anyway.
설마 공룡 분장은 안 하겠지
Tell me you're not gonna dress
like a dinosaur.
2년 연달아선 안 해
Not two years in a row.
- 참석은 하겠지만 분장은 안해
- 해야돼
-I'll come, but I'm not dressing up.
-You have to.
싫어, 할로윈은 너무 바보 같아
딴 사람 흉내나 내고 말야
No. Halloween is stupid. Dressing up,
pretending to be someone you're not.
넌 배우야
You're an actor.
로스, 모나 데려올 거야?
Ross, are you gonna bring Mona?
- 그럼, 그래야지
- 결혼식에서 만난 그 여자?
-I will.
-The girl from the wedding?
할로윈 분장을 하겠다면
비키니 모델 같은 걸로 하라고 해
If she needs costume ideas,
she could be a bikini model..
아니면 음탕한 간호사나
섹시한 치어리더
or a slutty nurse,
or a sexy cheerleader.
텍사스 전기톱 학살의 가죽 얼굴이
좋겠다, 아냐! 음탕한 가죽 얼굴
Or Leatherface from Texas Chainsaw
Massacre. No! Slutty Leatherface.
조이도 모나한테 반하지 않았었어?
Wasn't Joey hitting on her too?
맞아, 조이도 모나한테 반했었지
That's right, he was hitting on her.
그런데 내가 차지했어
더 잘난 놈이 차지하는 거야
And I got her. I guess
the better man won.
제발 모나 뺏아가지 마
Please don't take her from me.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'할로윈 파티'
우슬라!
Ursula!
잠깐만, 나야, 피비라구
Wait. It's me, Phoebe.
거울인 줄 알았어
알았어, 잘 가
I thought there was a mirror there.
Okay. Bye.
잠깐만!
Wait a second!
그래, 별일 없어?
So, what's new with you?
없어, 다음 주에 결혼해
Nothing.
I'm getting married next week.
뭐?
What?
조촐하게 할 거야
가족만 모아놓고
It'll be a small ceremony.
Just family.
그이 가족
His.
알았어
Okay.
정말 잘됐다
I'm happy for you.
잠깐만, 결혼식에
오고 싶으면 와도 돼
Wait. If you want to come,
I guess that'd be okay.
- 정말?
- 그럼
-Really?
-Sure.
와서 나랑 자매지간 하든지 해
You could be my sister for the day.
그래, 알았어
Yeah, okay.
이따가 밤에 친구 집에서
할로윈 파티가 있는데 너도 와
My friends are having a party tonight,
so you could come.
약혼자도 만나게 데려오구
Maybe I could meet the guy.
오늘밤엔 나 일해야 돼
Well, I'm supposed to work tonight.
사실 지금도 일할 시간이야
그러니 상관없지 뭐!
I'm supposed to be working now,
so who cares!
- 분장하고 와야 돼
- 그래서 너도...
-It's a costume party.
-So that's why you're..
아냐
No.
어쨌든 고마워
But thanks.
- 분장하고 오랬잖아
- 했어
-You're supposed to wear a costume.
-I am.
곧 몸이 불어나 입지도 못할 옷에
I am a woman who spent money
on a dress she wants to wear..
돈을 엄청나게 쓴 여자로 말야
because soon she won't
fit into it.
난 캣우먼이야, 네 몸이 불면
그 옷을 가로챌 악당이지
I'm Catwoman, who wants the dress
when you're too big for it.
- 사탕 주세요!
- 내가 줘도 돼?
-Trick or treat!
-Can I give out candy?
애들과 어울리고 싶어
임신한 후로 모성애가 샘솟아
I want to be with kids. Since I got
pregnant, I have maternal instincts.
- 사탕 주세요!
- 보채지 좀 마!
-Trick or treat!
-Just a minute!
이게 누구야!
Look at you guys!
- 무시무시한 마녀구나
- 고맙습니다
-Wow! You are a very scary witch.
-Thank you.
- 익살스런 광대네
- 고맙습니다
-And you are a very funny clown.
-Thank you.
그리고 넌...
And you..
유행 감각이 참 뛰어나기도 하지
are so in style right now.
내가 랄프 로렌에서 일하는데
올 가을 패션 경향이 이 승마복이야
I work at Ralph Lauren. The fall line
has got this equestrian theme.
- 설마 너 보그 표지...
- 그냥 사탕 주시면 안 돼요?
-Did you see the cover of Vogue..?
-Could I just have the candy?
받아
Sure.
캣우먼, 또 만났군
Catwoman. So we meet again.
그래, 슈퍼걸
So we do, Supergirl.
나야, 피비라구
It's me, Phoebe.
모니카, 얘기 좀 할까?
Monica, can I talk to you
for a second?
의상 구해준 건 고마워
I appreciate the costume.
네가 이랬어?
You did this to him?
맘에 들어할 줄 알았지
I thought he'd love it.
- 벨베틴 래빗을 좋아한단 말야
- 그 토끼는 흰색에 갈색이야
-He loves The Velveteen Rabbit.
-That rabbit was brown and white.
분홍이야, 싫으면 토끼 하지 마
It was pink, or no bunny at all.
토끼 하지 말래
나더러 늘 토끼 하지 말래!
No bunny at all.
Always no bunny at all!
- 너도 분장 안 했어?
- 했어, 챈들러로 말야
-You didn't dress up either?
-Yes, I did. I'm Chandler.
어떻게 된 거야?
Dude, what happened?
그게 어떻게 나야?
How is that me?
난 챈들러야
I'm Chandler.
너랑 똑같아!
That is so you!
- 내가 언제 그랬어?
-When have I ever done that?
사탕 주세요
Trick or treat.
- 세상에서 제일 예쁜 발레리나네
- 감사합니다
-You're the prettiest ballerina ever.
-Thank you.
하나 더 줘야겠는걸
That deserves another candy.
감사합니다
Thank you.
그건 사탕 4개감인걸
I have to say,
that earns "two-two" pieces of candy.
사랑해요!
I love you!
이거 다 가져
Honey, here, take it all.
모니카, 사탕 좀 더 줘
Monica? We need more candy.
- 4명밖에 안 왔었잖아
- 알아
-There's only been four kids.
-I know.
그런데 그 중 하나가
날 사랑한다기에 다 줬어
But one said she loved me,
so I gave her everything.
이러니 임신을 하지
No wonder you're pregnant.
- 뭘로 분장한 거야?
- 러시아 위성 스퍼트닉 기억나?
-What are you supposed to be?
-Remember the satellite, Sputnik?
좋아, 난 감자야, 감자는
영어로 스퍼드라고도 하지
Well, I'm a potato. Or a "spud"..
그리고 이건 안테나야
and these are my antenna.
스퍼드에 안테나가 붙어있으니까...
So Sputnik becomes..?
스퍼드닉이잖아!
Spud-nik!
난 최악의 분장에서 벗어났어
Wow! I don't have
the worst costume anymore.
좋아! 로스가 똥으로 분장했군
All right! Ross came as doodie.
- 똥이 아냐
- 아니지, 우주의 똥이야
-No, I'm not doodie.
-No, space-doodie.
난 스퍼드닉이라구
Okay, I'm Spud-nik.
- 스퍼트닉 알지?
- 스퍼트닉이 뭔데, 똥장군?
-You know, like Sputnik.
-What's a Sputnik, doodie-man?
자기
Hey, sweetie.
- 키스 안 해줄 거야?
- 해줄게요
-Aren't you gonna kiss me?
-Okay.
대신 키스 끝나고 나면
누군지 말해줘야 돼요
But right after, you have to tell me
who you are.
- 우슬라?
- 우슬라의 약혼자?
-Ursula?
-Ursula's fiance?
우슬라의 동생이군요
처제 될 사람의 엉덩이를 때렸네
You're the sister. I just slapped
my future sister-in-law's ass.
어머니도 오셨어요?
그쪽 엉덩이도 때릴 수 있는데
Is your mother here?
I could slap her on the butt.
- 엄마는 자살하셨어요
- 봐, 다 알면서 말야
-My mother killed herself.
-See, and I knew that.
땀 나네
Now I'm sweating.
땀이 나요, 이러고 있다간
더 날 것 같아, 그만 가볼게요
I'm sweating. Now I'm saying look
at me, I'm even sweatier. I should go.
가긴요, 다시 시작하면 되죠
No. We'll start over.
- 안녕, 난 피비예요
- 에릭이에요
-Hi, I'm Phoebe.
-Eric.
- 왜 그런 식으로 쳐다보죠?
- 땀이 눈으로 들어가서 아파요
-Why are you looking at me like that?
-Sweat's burning my eyes.
- 고마워요
- 닦으세요
-Thank you.
-There.
- 뭐죠?
- 달리 명칭은 없어요
-What are you?
-There's no name for it.
그냥 긴장되고
땀이 비오듯 흘러요
I get nervous, and I sweat like crazy.
- 아니, 그 분장 말예요
- 태양계예요
-No, I meant your costume.
-I'm a solar system.
우리 2학년 애들이 도와줬죠
My second graders helped.
- 난 2학년이 너무 좋아요
- 정말요?
-I love the second grade.
-Really?
1학년보다 훨씬 낫잖아요
3학년보단 확실히 낫구요
It's much better than first grade,
and definitely better than third.
걔들은 정치에 신경전에
아주 복잡해요
With all the politics
and the mind games.
- 직업이 뭐예요?
- 안마사요, 낮에는요
-So, what do you do?
-I'm a masseuse, by day.
- 나랑 같이 안 있어줘도 돼요
- 재밌는데요 뭐
-You don't have to stand with me.
-I'm having fun.
- 우슬라와 결혼한다니 기뻐요
- 운이 좋았죠, 멋진 여자예요
-I'm excited for you and Ursula.
-I feel very lucky. She's great.
- 세상에서 가장 아름답죠
- 고마워요
-She's the most beautiful woman ever.
-Thank you.
- 조이?
- 왜?
-Hey, Joey?
-Yeah?
- 만화책 보지?
- 만화책만 보지
-You read comic books, right?
-Exclusively.
캣우먼이랑 슈퍼걸이 싸우면
누가 이겨?
Who would win in a fight,
Catwoman or Supergirl?
- 아무래도 캣우먼이지
- 좋았어
-Catwoman, hands down.
-Yeah.
그런데 너랑 피비랑 싸우면
피비가 이길걸
Between you and Phoebe?
I'd give Phoebe the edge.
- 뭐? 진심이야?
- 말이라고 해?
-What? Really?
-You kidding?
피비는 노숙자였어
게다가 성깔이 대단하다구
Phoebe lived on the street, okay?
Plus, she's got a crazy temper.
피비가 뒤에 와있는 거 아니지?
She's not right behind me, is she?
걱정하지 마
No, you're fine.
- 그럼 레이첼한텐 이길까?
- 글쎄
-Could I take Rachel?
-I'm not sure.
뭐? 나도 한 터프해!
What? Come on, I am tough!
내 배를 있는 힘껏 내리쳐 봐!
Punch me here, as hard as you can!
진정해, 뭐가 그렇게 심각해?
중요한 일도 아니잖아
Relax. Why are you so serious?
It doesn't matter.
그래? 로스랑 챈들러가 너보다
힘세다고 하면 뭐라고 할래?
Really? What if I told you
Ross or Chandler could beat you up?
'아줌마, 됐어'
I would say, "Woman, please."
우슬라의 약혼자 정말 근사해
Ursula's fiance is really sweet.
- 붙으면 이길 것 같아?
- 가슴에 방울 단 친구?
-You think you could take him?
-The dude with the balls on his chest?
물론이지
I think so.
어쩌다 언니랑 엮였지?
저렇게 근사한데 말야
But what is he doing with my sister?
He's so great.
선생님인 데다 자원 봉사도 한대
He's a teacher,
he does volunteer work.
땀 많이 나는 남자 원랜 별로지만
저 정도면 구석구석 닦아주겠어
Normally, I don't like sweaty guys.
But I could just mop him up.
- 맙소사, 피비?
- 왜?
-Oh, my God, Phoebe?
-What?
- 언니 약혼자한테 반했구나
- 난 아냐, 반한 건 너지!
-You're getting a crush on him.
-No, I'm not, you are!
성깔 나온다
Here comes the temper.
사탕 주세요
Trick or treat.
어쩌지? 사탕이 다 떨어졌어
그래서 누가 사러 갔단다
Know what? We're out of candy.
But someone went for more.
그 동안 사탕 대신 돈을 줬는데
돈도 다 떨어지고 없네
And I've been giving out money,
but I'm out of that too.
- 수표를 써주면 안 될까?
- 좋아요
-Can I write you a check?
-Okay.
- 좋아, 이름이 뭐지?
- 를라니 메이욜라노파비치요
-Okay. What's your name?
-Lelani Mayolanofavich.
그냥 현금이라고 쓸게
Okay, I'm just gonna write this out
to "cash."
- 안녕
- 안녕, 모나
-Hi.
-Hi, Mona.
조이가 기쁘겠어요, 당신이 음탕한
간호사로 분장했으면 했거든요
Joey's gonna be thrilled. He was
hoping you'd be a slutty nurse.
사실 난 그냥 간호사예요
Actually, I'm just a nurse.
그 말에 내가 당황할 줄 알겠지만
난 이미 갈 데까지 갔거든요
You'd think that would embarrass me,
but I'm maxed out.
- 어서 와
- 잠깐만
-You made it.
-Wait.
- 감자야?
- 감자란 뜻의 스퍼드에...
-You're a potato?
-Well, I'm a spud..?
- 안테나라, 스퍼드닉이구나!
- 맞았어!
-And the antenna.. You're Spud-nik!
-Yes!
둘이 결혼해
Marry her.
그럼 말해 봐, 로스랑 챈들러랑
싸우면 누가 이길 것 같아?
Here's a good one. Who'd win
a fight between Ross and Chandler?
난 말 못해, 챈들러는 남편이야
I can't answer that.
Chandler's my husband.
- 로스가 이긴다구?
- 그래
-So Ross?
-Yeah.
- 안녕, 공주님
- 안녕, 왕자님
-Hey, beautiful.
-Hello, handsome.
맙소사
Oh, God.
두 사람 좀 봐
둘이 언제 처음 만났죠?
Look at you two.
When did you guys meet?
- 2주 전에요
- 겨우 2주요?
-Two weeks ago.
-That's it?
알아요, 미친 짓 같겠죠
원래 충동적인 사람은 아닌데
I know. It sounds crazy,
and I'm not impulsive, but..
- 우린 공통점이 많거든요
- 그래요?
-we have so much in common.
-Oh, really?
우선 둘 다 선생이죠
We're both teachers.
- 평화 봉사단 활동도 했어요
- 그래요?
-And we were both in the Peace Corps.
-Peace Corps, really?
우루과이에서 봉사할 때 옆옆 마을에
있으면서도 마주친 적이 한번도 없죠
When we were building in Uruguay,
we were two towns apart and never met.
맞아, 내가 갔을 땐 마을이
아니었는데 떠날 땐 마을이었거든
Yeah. It wasn't a town when I got
there, but it was a town when I left.
- 이제 술에 좀 취해볼까?
- 그래
-Shall we get me really drunk?
-Sure.
안녕, 똥장군
Howdy, doodie.
재밌네
That's funny, yeah.
여기 있는 사람들 중 제일 재밌어
마누라 때문에 토끼 옷 입은 놈아
You're the funniest man here in a
bunny costume his wife made him wear.
진정해, 물을 심하게 내려
핏기가 하나도 없잖아
Relax, man. You're looking
a little flushed.
- 잘하면 궁금증이 풀리겠어
- 궁금증이라니?
-Our question might get answered.
-What question?
너랑 로스랑 싸우면
누가 이길까 얘길 하고 있었어
Who could kick whose ass in a fight,
you or Ross?
- 물어보나마나야
- 너도 로스라고 생각하는구나?
-There's no question.
-So you think Ross too?
- 로스 편을 들었어?
- 로스는 힘이 세
-You picked Ross?
-Ross is strong.
세 사람 중에서 힘이 제일 셀걸
조이 다음으로 말야
He's the strongest out of all three
of you. Except for Joey.
- 날 배신하다니 믿을 수가 없어
- 모니카 말이 맞아, 내가 더 세
-I can't believe you didn't pick me.
-She's right. I am stronger.
널 파멸시킬 수도 있어
I would destroy you.
그래? 네가 더 세다구?
한번 증명해보지 그래?
Really? You think you're stronger?
Why don't you prove it?
수학 공식 증명하듯 증명해주지!
I'll prove it like a theorem!
그만 해! 그만!
All right! Stop it!
그만! 우리 집에서 싸움은 안 돼
Stop! No one's gonna fight.
싸움 구경하러 온 사람들이야
그냥 구경하게 놔둬!
People came to see a fight,
let's give them one!
- 팔씨름으로 겨뤄봐요
- 음탕한 간호사 말 들어
-You guys could arm-wrestle.
-Listen to the slutty nurse.
- 네가 밀릴걸
- 그래? 넌 시내까지 밀릴걸
-You're going down.
-Oh, yeah? You're going downtown!
그런 상스러운 대화는
정말이지 너무 쪽 팔려
Seriously, guys, the trash talk
is embarrassing.
건터, 사탕을 사왔군요
정말 너무 고마워
Gunther, you brought candy.
Thank you so much.
- 너무 근사해
- 정말?
-You are so sweet.
-Really?
당신 애인이 될 남자는
이 세상 최고의 행운아야
You are gonna make some man
the luckiest guy in the world.
- 가볼게요
- 사탕 주세요
-Got to go.
-Trick or treat.
안녕! 사탕 여기 있다
Hi! Wow! There you go.
제 친구 루이스 말이
여기선 돈을 준다던데요
My friend Lewis told me
you were giving out money.
그랬지, 그런데 사탕을 사왔거든
We were, but now we've got candy.
전 돈으로 받을래요
I'd rather have the money.
네 맘대로 할 수 있는 게 아냐
할로윈 재밌게 보내라!
That's not your choice.
Happy Halloween!
불공평해요
This isn't fair.
망토 하나 두르고 와서
사탕 공짜로 타 가는 건 공평하고?
Is it fair that you put on a cape
and get stuff?
닥쳐요!
Shut up!
너나 닥쳐!
You shut up!
- 나한테 그런 말하면 안 돼요
- 방금 했는데 어쩔까나
-You can't tell me to shut up.
-I think I just did.
게다가 또 나오고 있네, 닥쳐!
And here it comes again. Shut up!
나 잘하고 있어, 걱정 마
No, I got it. I'm good. I got it.
잠깐, 할 말이 하나 남았어
그게 뭐냐면, 닥쳐!
Wait, I had one more thing to say.
Right. Shut up.
진짜 못된 아줌마야
You're a mean old woman.
잠깐! 닥쳐! 울지마!
Wait! Shut.. Don't cry!
수표 써줄게!
Let me get my checkbook!
이럴 필요 없어
제일 중요한 건 내면이야
You don't have to do this. The
strength inside you means the most.
자긴 성실하지, 정직하지
게다가 인격도 뛰어나
You're loyal, you're honest
and you have integrity.
내가 원하는 힘은 그런 거라구
That's the strength I want in a man.
난 아냐, 붙어!
That means nothing to me. Come on!
- 거짓말쟁이
- 안녕
-Hi, liar.
-Hey.
에릭이 너랑 결혼하려는 이유는
네 말이 사실인 줄 알기 때문이야
He's marrying you because he thinks
the things you were saying were true.
- 사실일 수도 있어
- 하지만 사실이 아닌걸
-They could be true.
-But they're not.
차이가 좀 있네
It's a fine line.
- 왜 거짓말을 해?
- 나도 모르겠어
-Why are you lying?
-I don't know.
자기가 한 일을 나도 했다니까
무지 흥분하더라구, 재밌더라
He did this stuff, I said I did it too.
He got so excited, it was fun.
이러면 안돼
에릭의 인생을 망치는 거야
You can't do this.
You're gonna ruin his life.
뭐가 그렇게 심각해?
그냥 결혼일 뿐이잖아
Why are you taking this so seriously?
It's just a marriage.
게다가 바람 피게 되면
부적절한 관계라 부를 텐데 뭐
Besides, if I cheat on him,
I can call it an affair.
자기?
Honey?
이건 지저분한 습관이야
당장 담배를 끊도록 해!
It's a disgusting habit,
and I want you to quit now!
우슬라 덕분에 금연한 사람 많죠
She's helped so many people quit.
우리 그만 가
We'd better get going.
- 오늘 교회 모임 있댔잖아
- 그러네
-You have a church group meeting.
-Right.
- 반가웠어요
- 나두요
-It was nice meeting you.
-You too.
우슬라, 만나서 정말 반가웠어!
And, Ursula, it was really nice
meeting you tonight!
빨리 와! 토끼랑 똥장군이랑
붙는대, 다들 기다려
Come on! Bunny versus doodie.
We're waiting!
좋아, 한판승으로 해
상품은 모두 승자 거야
Okay, guys. One match,
winner take all.
잠깐, 상품을 뭘로 하지?
Wait. What does the winner get?
- 자존심
- 존엄성
-Pride.
-And dignity.
너희 뜻이 그렇다면야
Okay, if you say so.
자, 준비하시고 시작!
All right, ready, set, go!
- 이겨라!
- 힘내!
-Come on!
- 둘 다 힘세네요
- 아니면 둘 다 약하거나요
-Wow, they're both really strong.
-Or equally weak.
세상에, 챈들러 말야
섹스할 때의 표정이야
Oh, God. Chandler's making
his sex face.
- 지치지 않아?
- 아니, 하루 종일 할 수도 있어
-So you getting tired?
-No. I could do this all day.
나도 그래
Yeah. Me too.
- 그런데 좀 지치긴 해
- 난 현기증 나
-Getting a little tired, though.
-God, I'm exhausted.
내 꼴이 말이 아니게 생겼어
모나가 저기 서있잖아
This is starting to look bad for me,
okay? Mona's standing right there.
조이랑 얘길 하네!
그냥 나한테 좀 져줘!
She's talking to Joey!
You gotta let me win!
너야말로, 마누라가 날
약골로 안다구
Let me win.
My wife thinks I'm a wimp.
그래도 넌 마누라나 있지
난 이혼도 하고 임신도 시켰어
At least you have a wife.
I get divorces and knock people up.
게다가 똥장군이고 말야
And I'm dressed as doodie.
- 스퍼드닉이라며
- 스퍼드닉은 무슨, 똥장군이야
-You're Spud-nik.
-Come on, who we kidding? I'm doodie.
부탁해, 모나가 보잖아
Please? She's watching.
- 알았어
- 고마워
-Fine.
-Thanks.
- 이런
- 이겼다!
-Oh, no.
-Oh, yeah!
자기 멋져!
My hero!
정말 이상한 여자네
You're a weird lady.
우슬라가 핸드백을 놓고 왔대요
Ursula said she left her purse.
다행이에요, 기도해줘야 할 사람
전화번호가 들어있거든요
What a relief. It has the numbers
for her prayer chain.
그렇겠죠
I'm sure it does.
그럼 결혼식 때 봐요
Guess I'll see you at the wedding.
결혼식에는 참석 못할 것 같아요
I don't think I'm gonna make it
to the wedding.
모든 행운이 함께 하길 바랄게요
I wish you all the luck in the world.
그리고 이건 결혼할 사람들한테
And I also want to give you
a little piece of advice..
항상 해주는 충고인데
that I give to everyone
who's getting married.
아내를 믿지 마세요
Don't trust your wife.
우린 괜찮을 거예요
I think we'll be okay.
아주 완벽하거든요
날 위해 순결을 지켜왔대요
It's so perfect,
and she's been saving herself for me.
- 안 되겠어, 다 거짓말이에요
- 네?
-I can't let you do this. She's lying.
-What?
우슬라는 거짓말쟁이라구요
증명해 보이죠, 잠깐만요
She is lying. And I bet
I could prove it. Excuse me.
보세요, 기도자 명단 아니잖아요
Okay. Yeah, not a prayer chain.
무슨 은행 설계도 같이 생겼네요
But what looks like a detailed drawing
of a bank floor plan.
보세요, 우슬라의 명찰이에요
우슬라는 식당에서 일하죠
Here's the name tag from
where she works as a waitress.
선생이 아니라 웨이트리스라구요
Not a teacher, a waitress.
여기 운전 면허증이 있네
우슬라는 늘 나이를 속이죠
Here, she always lies about this.
- 자기가 몇 살이래요?
- 25살이오
-How old did she say she was?
-She told me she was 25.
이건 보여주지 말까 봐
I almost don't want to show you.
이것만 명심해요
난 우슬라보다 1분 어려요
Just remember, I'm a minute younger.
난 정말 바보예요
I am so stupid.
선생이 아닌 게 당연한데 말예요
Of course she's not a teacher.
'스파이 자녀 전용 특급 비밀 학교'
같은 게 있을 리가 없잖아요
There's no such thing as a "Top Secret
School for the Children of Spies."
당신은 바보 아녜요
No, you're not stupid.
똑똑하지도 않아요
I'm not smart.
한번이라도 충동적으로
뭔가를 해보고 싶었어요
I just wanted so much
to be impulsive for once.
- 낭만적으로 말예요
- 좋죠
-To be romantic.
-Good.
충동적이고 낭만적인 것 말예요
상대를 잘못 선택한 것뿐이에요
You should be impulsive and romantic.
You did it with the wrong person.
- 왜요?
- 이상해요, 얼굴은 똑같은데
-What?
-It's weird, two people look so alike.
성격은 다르니 말예요
And so different.
에릭! 어서 가!
Eric! Let's go!
- 가서 해결할게요
- 네, 그래요
-Better go deal with it.
-Yeah, you should.
서둘러! 빨리 가서 기도해야 돼!
Hurry up! I gotta pray!
우는 거 달래느라 50불을 썼어
I had to give the kid
50 bucks to stop crying.
그 정도면 괜찮네
That's not bad.
여자 친구라 속이고
몇 집 방문도 하고 말야
I also had to go to a few houses
as his girlfriend.
난 정말 애 다루는 덴 형편없어
I am awful with children.
잘하고 있는데 뭘
할로윈엔 애들이 원래 그래
You're good with kids.
They're just crazy on Halloween.
탐욕스럽게 사탕에 착 달라붙지
They're all greedy,
hopped up on sugar.
- 정말 그럴까?
- 그럼
-That's all it is?
-Absolutely.
할로윈이 제일 힘들어
성탄절만 빼고, 생일만 빼고
Halloween is the worst. Except
for Christmas. And their birthdays.
여름에도 애들이 좀 날뛰긴 해
They get crazy during the summer too.
그리고 배고플 때랑 졸릴 때도
And any time they're
hungry or sleepy.
애 키우는 건 힘들어
행운을 빌어
Kids are tough.
Good luck with that.
팔씨름에서 진거 정말 안됐어
Look, I'm sorry you lost.
이건 비밀인데 일부러 져준 거야
I got a secret for you.
I let him win.
비밀이야, 거짓말이야?
Was that a secret, or a lie?
- 정말이야, 로스?
- 왜?
-No, I let him.. Ross?
-Yeah?
내가 져준 거라고 말 좀 해줄래?
Would you tell her
I let you win, please?
챈들러가 나한테 '일부러 져줬어'
Chandler "let me win."
챈들러가 얼마나 힘이 센데
팔이 다 아프네, 간호사?
No, Chandler's really strong.
My arm is so sore. Oh, nurse?
나 힘세다구, 보여줄게
I am strong. I'll show you.
챈들러, 됐어
Chandler, please.
왜 그래? 겁나?
What's the matter? Scared?
붙어, 큰 토끼!
Let's go, big bunny!
하나, 둘, 셋, 시작!
One, two, three. Go!
나 자살할래!
I'm gonna kill myself!